{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\AprilQuiz.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "Io ho tre fratelli e due sorelle.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "I have 3 brothers and 2 sisters.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Ecco la mia famiglia.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Here is my family.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "a sinistra",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "On the left.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "a destra",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "On the right.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "sempre dritto",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "straight ahead",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Che un ristorante qui vicino.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Is there a restaurant near by?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "il prima piatto",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "The first plate.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "il contorno",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "the side dish",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Vorrei il conto per favore.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "I would like the bill, please.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Posso pagare con certa di credito.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "May I pay with a credit card?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Vorrei un'insalata e un dolce.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "I take a salad, a dessert.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Lui paga tutto.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "He pays all.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Prendo una rosto di maiale con potate al forno.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "I take a pork roast with backed potatoes.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Viviamo in la periferia.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "We live in the outskirts.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Parliamo Italiano solo un po'.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "We speak Italian only a litte.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Non cpisco, ripite per piacere.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "I don't understand, please repeat.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Cosa significa?",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What does it mean?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Che giorno e' oggi?",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What day is today?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Sono le due e un quarto.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "it is 2 and 15 minutes.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "A che ora parte il treno.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "At what time does the train leave?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Che lavoro fai?",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "What job do you do?",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "fare bella figura",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "To make a good impression.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "fare brutto figura",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "To make a bad impression.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "fare la collazione",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "To have breakfast.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "Vivono in campagna.",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "They live in the country.",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "io vado, lui va",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "I go, he goes",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "noi andiamo",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "We go",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "solito",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "Usually",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "sempre",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "always",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "mai",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "never",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "a volte",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "sometimes",
            "tried": 0
        },
        {
            "answer": "spesso",
            "failed": 0,
            "question": "often",
            "tried": 0
        }
    ]
}